This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
Fighting alongside Whitebeard and his associates,
he continues to push toward the scaffold.
As the all-out battle continues between the Navy's elite
and the strongest pirates in the world,
Luffy puts his life on the line, vowing death before defeat.
Concerned about the future?
I'll be more than happy to show it to you now.
Let's end this.
Execute him!
I'm too slow!
Don't make me laugh!
You think I can't stop those ruts from doing it?
Don't use ruts from doing it!
Don't you dare!
Don't use ruts from doing war.
Did you just do what I think you did?
It's the conqueror's... spirit!
Well, damn. This is a mess.
There's a surprise for you.
Why that little brat?
The scaffold at last! The way to Ace has opened!
We're good! Ace is still alive, guys!
Hey, pull it together, pal. That power, it came from Ace's brother, huh?
What the...?
I almost passed out back there.
That was the Conqueror's spirit, like Pops and Shanks use.
Damn, that kid is full of surprises, huh?
I don't think he realizes what he just did.
I tell you, boys, we got some scary stuff right here.
He didn't learn that power. He was born with it.
Just like Pops.
If your will is weak, stand back. He's not just another rookie. Conqueror's spirit, huh?
We can't forget he's the son of Dragon. That's what we get for underestimating him.
What next, Vice Admiral?
My energy hormones didn't do that. What hat did you pull those powers out of?
Power? What do you mean?
We'll discuss it later.
He's not aware of it. That means we can't count on him using it again.
Either way, it's no wonder the people are so drawn to him.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree, does it?
Dragon.
Do not let that boy escape this battlefield. If he does, he'll turn into a dire threat to us.
Dead or alive, you take him down!
No!
Scared to death of a mere boy and an old man? You were so cocky before, but where's your fire now?
I thought you wanted to kill me!
Focus on Whitebeard first! He may be a monster, but he's injured! Take him down, then go for the kid!
Hmm. Just try it.
Don't let a single marine lay a hand on him!
Don't be intimidated! Go!
They're aiming for Whitebeard! Move those buns while you still can!
After Straw Hat! Hurry!
Hurry!
Sir!
Uh...
Um...
Huh?
Ah!
We finally make headway and the bastards start pulling it together.
Thinks he can push through.
He'll be pushing up daisies first.
Damn it all.
Crap. Come on.
I can't help them.
As long as I've got these things on.
Hey, Pops. We got your back, so don't overdo it.
Stop and listen to me.
What's wrong?
There's a new plan.
I'm either gonna live or I'm gonna die.
So back up Straw Hat with everything you've got.
Ace's brother? Why?
What the hell?
Stop your gawking and take out Straw Hat already.
They're coming straight at you. Watch out!
I know you.
You're Doma, the Bohemian Knight, correct?
Vice Admiral Momonga. Pleasure to meet you.
We're the Kelvin brothers. It sucks to be you.
You gotta fight us!
Thunder Lord McGuy.
Pardon me, Vice Admiral, but I require a moment of your time if you would.
We've got some friends.
If Whitebeard says to lend you a hand, then we're on it in a flash.
Ace is right there, Straw Hat.
No way they're gonna stop all of us.
Yeah!
Whitebeard's allies are backing up Straw Hat.
This does not look good.
Who are you guys?
Never mind that. Keep running.
The Navy forces are focused on Pops right now.
So this might be your only chance to slip past the Admirals and move in.
We're sniping them all at once, so wait for your opening!
Hey, not bad. I think they like you.
The greatest pirate in the world gave his seal of approval.
Huh?
Yee-haw!
Ace may be your brother, but he's Whitebeard's son, you know, and trusts you with his life.
So why don't you stop trying to be coy and rise to the occasion, you cocky little snot?
I don't care what that old man wants, and I don't care what he thinks either!
I only came here to do one thing!
I don't need anyone's approval for that!
The pirates are gaining headway on us!
They're about to break through! We need backup in a hurry!
With all due respect, maybe we should change plans!
Not yet. If we have a chance to defeat Whitebeard, then we must take it!
Everyone move in now!
If he falls, then it's only a matter of time for the rest of them!
One or one hundred doesn't matter.
You can stand in line, or you can all die at once!
He's still up! What's it going to take?
We think alike, brat. As long as Ace goes home, nothing else matters.
Show me the will of Dee. Show me the future.
Even if my days are numbered, I can see tomorrow blazing through this battlefield.
Uh, Hawkeye! This could get nasty!
It's the president's order. For now, we're still allies. Go!
Mr. One, I believe.
Look out!
Crocodile Two?
Stop sleeping on the job, Mr. One.
Uh, I thought it was like old times, but maybe prison made me soft.
You are needed here, Straw Hat. Get moving, before I change my mind.
This won't end well. Are you certain?
I'm not in the mood to put up with your crap or anyone else's.
If you want to fight, then shut up and do it.
Luffy! I'm here!
I'll do everything in my power to aid you.
Target is Monkey D. Luffy. Open fire.
Boa Hancock. In sight. Aborting the attack.
That's enough!
Are you out of your damn mind?
This isn't the first time you've gotten in the way, but it will be the last.
What are you trying to accomplish here, anyway?
You're going to lose your warlord status.
You foolish, misshapen man-child.
Your ignorance is an affront to my beauty.
My what now?
I shall set a pearl of wisdom before you.
Love is always a hurricane, you little pig!
You're insane, aren't you?
You better run, Straw Hat.
So what's going on, Captain?
You don't seem too happy right now.
I'm not. It doesn't look good out there.
All of you saw it, right?
How incredible I was on my broadcast.
The whole world should be watching me.
But nobody cares!
They're too busy gawking at that chump running to the scaffold to face their eyes on whatever
awesome thing I happen to be doing.
Now answer me this, who should be the star of this pirate show?
That would be you, of course.
Damn straight it should be me.
Now I've got to do something flashy in a flash so people stop watching Straw Hat's shenanigans
and pay attention to mine.
Hey, fork over that snail, pal.
Oh yeah, about that.
The snail.
It's kind of frozen solid right now.
What a pain!
Just defrost the damn thing.
Give it a quick dip in that magma water or whatever and the ice should melt right off.
It melted, all right.
Nice!
Let me see.
Good as new.
Here.
It's all gross!
What did you do?
Oh yeah, salt water and snails don't get along, do they?
After we went to all that trouble to steal it from the Navy, too.
Well, it's not going to win any beauty contests, but the thing might still work.
I'll just try to sweet-talk it a bit.
Hey, little buddy, think you could open those peepers for me?
We're going to be best buddies, okay?
What?
I was nice!
It's because of your scary faces, you bunch of goons.
Sorry, I was born this way.
I guess good looks don't run in my family.
Damn it.
Once Straw Hat makes it to that scaffold, nobody's going to care about anything else.
I've got to do something distracting.
Fire!
Make a path to the scaffold!
We only need one moment to break through!
Getting desperate, are they?
They're going to danger, noo, noo, noo!
That's enough.
Fishman Karate!
Arabesque Brickfish!
Jinbei, I can handle this, dammit.
I said to leave me and help Straw Hat get to the scaffold, didn't I?
Sorry friend, but I'm not one of your pirates.
That means I don't have to listen to a word you say.
Have it your way then.
They did it! They cleared a path!
Everyone else has already done their part, now you do yours!
Keep on running and don't look back!
For better or worse, it's our turn now.
Look, I'm sorry to make you do this when I know you're still recovering,
but we need your skills in particular.
No apologies necessary, I assure you.
I shall give it my best.
I'll try!
See you later!
I'll find the world.
How is that?!
spikes fishing
두들
liegt
They made a bridge!
It's Sinasuma of the Revolutionary Army!
Is that handy or what? Thanks!
Straw Hutt's headed straight for the scaffold! Stop him!
Sorry, too busy to do it myself!
What are you doing? Block his path!
We can't, sir! See? These pirates are blocking us! We can't get past!
Fools! Use your guns! Cannoneers open fire!
Damn, it's them!
The Whitebeard Pirates Team of Commanders!
Pop said to watch your back! So keep running! We got this!
Everyone push! We're breaking through!
You!
Here he comes, man!
Come, come!
Battleaxe!
Take it straight to the top!
You got it! Thanks!
He's getting away!
Death wing!
If you really want to rumble, then step right up!
Hee-haw!
Now you just keep on shining, Straw Boy!
It worked! He's gonna make it!
We got this! We really got this!
It's not over! Pull him down!
Straw Hat! Savings!
Yeah, it's all you from here on out!
I've got to admit, I didn't think Whitebeard would gamble it all on you.
It's been a fun ride!
But don't kid yourself, boy!
Well, don't that beat all!
It's gonna be a good show!
Why don't you just sit back and watch?
Luffy!
We did it!
I'm here!
Whoa!
Is Garp gonna fight too?
Grandpa!
Get out of the way!
I'm not moving a damned inch!
I'm a Vice Admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting pirates since long before you were born!
And I ain't stopping today!
Oh, man!
You're not my grandson here!
You are the pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
And I'll fight you to the death!
This is the path that you chose to take!
You and your brother alike!
Thanks to Inazuma's makeshift bridge, Luffy is able to ascend to the scaffold.
Garp, unable to watch any longer, leaps into Luffy's path.
Maintaining his pride as a Marine, he faces his own grandson in battle, cursing the life of piracy that Luffy and Ace chose.
On the next, Wood Piece!
Each on different paths!
Luffy versus Garp!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
I know nancy sent you back at the end of the л
Exactly!
I know at the end of the day, you all saw us epidermid or in battle!
If you're taking a 리 기자 to play this eye with me, I didn't really wanna puke you!